codrutturcanu.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter such as your e-mail address.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To send periodic emails to our newsletter subscribers and blog readers

In addition, you might receive occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We use AWeber’s [PermissionPledge](http://www.aweber.com/permission.htm) ™ to protect your privacy and inbox; we also use Google’s FeedBurner mailing service for blog updates.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. In addition to e-mail address, our analytics trackers may also collect information such as the operating system you are working on, the Internet browser you are using, and the screen resolution of your computer.

It’s your option to enable or disable cookies in your browser.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
**  
Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Privacy Policy Created by [Free Privacy Policy](http://)
